If the industry is in love with the natural hair, guess who's going to have natural hair?
I remember that era for you.
You see, I got green now.
Oh, people want color?
Oh, Kim Wiley going to give you color.
But you see, okay, so for those who are listening, though, I think, I don't want, I don't want
you, I don't want you to misinterpret this as someone who is a chameleon, but more so
it's like, if you know who you are and you're solid and you are, and who you are, then you
can shapeshift without moving, without like dismantling the core.
Yes, that is absolutely true because I am a student of the business.
So I am just watching the trends.
Like you said, TikTok.
Wait, no, I'm going to step it up for you real quick.
Go, step it up, step it up, step it up.
Come on.
You don't just know the business, you know the game.
That's what it is.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Need I say more, less, nothing.
I didn't realize that I didn't want to play the game until I learned the game.
Then I was like, oh, you hate this.
You should go do radio.
And so I did.
And so I am.
Please leave me alone.
I still say nothing else to me.
These bitches are trash.